

Mayra Yamel Veras Diaz

Social Media Marketing Manager

Pávaro, La Altagracia, Dominican Republic

mverasdiaz@gmail.com

Profile

Experienced Social Media Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the hospitality industry. Strong media and communication professional skilled in OS X, WordPress, Instagram, Customer Relationship Management (CRM), and Hospitality Industry.

I'm well-versed in leading a team, brand management, brand development, digital marketing, content marketing, marketing strategy, email marketing, partner and agency relationships, project management, social media channels, and brand activation.

Employment History

Sept. 2019 - Present

Santo Domingo, DN

Sales Manager at Iesec Human

Jan 2019 – Aug 2019

Bávaro, La Altagracia

Info-Call Center Manager at Majestic Resorts

Apr 2016 - Jan 2019

Bávaro, La Altagracia

Social Media Manager at Majestic Resorts

- Prepare the strategy for the brand to follow in social media.
- · Design the presence in all social media outlets.
- In charge of carrying out viral campaigns and advertising in social networks.
- Control of accounts and interpretation of metric reports to evaluate ROI.

Jan 2015 – Apr 2016

Bávaro, La Altagracia

Community Manager at Majestic Resorts

- Provided response to guest reviews on Tripadvisor.
- Managing and updating social networks.
- Monitoring and tracking of third-party publications in social networks.
- Providing great customer service through social media.
- · Analysis of results and preparation of reports.

Nov 2015 - Nov 2016

Bávaro, La Altagracia

Community Manager at Helidosa

- · Provided response to guest reviews on TripAdvisor.
- Managing and updating social networks.
- Monitoring and tracking of third-party publications in social networks
- · Providing great customer service through social media.
- · Analysis of results and preparation of reports.

Details

C/Andrés Avelino Garcia #14, Naco

Santo Domingo, DN, DR

829-383-0854

Nationality

Dominican

Skills

Social Media

Customer Service

.

.

Fluent in English

Business English

Content Management

Hospitality Industry

.

Public Relations

Social Media Marketing

Advertising

Customer Satisfaction

Customer Care

Strategic Planning

Marketing Strategy

Marketing Communications

Microsoft Office Suite

Nov 2013 - Jan 2015

Bávaro, La Altagracia

Community Manager at Royalton Luxury Resorts

Responsible for maintaining and updating all existing Royalton Punta Cana and Memories Splash media channels including, but not limited to; Facebook, Twitter, TripAdvisor, Pinterest, Instagram, Google+ and all other relevant and emerging platforms. Updates and maintenance should include timesensitive information pertaining to our hotels, responding to guest inquiries as well as monitoring brand mentions for new business potential.

Education

2017 - 2018

Santo Domingo, DN

Hootsuite Academy

Social Marketing Certification

Industry-recognized certification that demonstrates your expertise with the essential elements of social marketing to clients and employers.

2012 - 2012

Santo Domingo, DN

Iesec Human República Dominicana

Coaching Certification

Our Certification allows the exercise as an independent professional, complements the managerial skills and leads to personal transformation.

2007 - 2007

New York University (NYU)

New York, NY

Public Relations Certificate

The Certificate in Strategic Media Communications serves to provide foundational public relations knowledge for anyone interested in PR, but it also is ideally suited for marketing professionals who need public relations knowledge to remain current in their industry.

2000 - 2004

Universidad Iberoamericana (UNIBE)

Santo Domingo, DN

Bachelor's degree, Advertising

Leadership and Teamwork Computer Networking Web Content Management French Language • • • • • • • • Italian Language • • • • • • • • Adobe Photoshop Adobe InDesign • • • • • • • • • Adobe Illustrator • • • • • • • • • Adobe Lightroom Digital Photography **Editing Video**